Mr. Bernard!
MR. BERNARD!
Where's Teach?!
We need to get him here, fast!
The boss won't be coming for us.
This is a battle we have to win on our own.
There he is!
Is he okay?
He's breathing.
He's going to make it.
You just said that Klaus wasn't here.
What did you mean?
Exactly what I said.
So, that's what's up.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Teach came and visited us all the time.
That was Grete in disguise.
All those times we saw Teach, it was always just Grete.
So wait, when we ran into him that one time...
And that meeting I had...
That's right.
You didn't just disguise yourself
as the assassin with the birthmark,
but as Teach, too?
I memorized the way the boss breathes,
the way he blinks,
and the position of every hair on his head.
Damn, you're really somethin' else!
I do happen to be plenty good at crossdressing.
Are you still mad about that?
In any case, the boss is at
a different mission site right now.
What mission?
The assassin hunt.
Corpse was never the one hiding in the mansion.
It was his associate, Olivia.
Teach wants us to capture Olivia
while he goes and fights Corpse.
That about sum it up?
It does.
So, Teach is all on his own again?
That whole thing about picking four people was a lie?
That was no lie.
He picked four people just fine.
Thea, Monika, Annette, Erna:
Those were the four he took with him to go kill Corpse.
We're the team members who got left out.
We didn't make the cut.
Magnificent.
It's me.
I left Grete with a message to pass along to you.
I'm sorry for tricking you.
Making the enemy spy lurking in the mansion
think that I was close at hand
was the best way I had of protecting you.
With any luck, it should have held them in check.
Also, there was a very specific reason
Embrace the toll of pain
I didn't bring you along.
The scabs that will never fade
The four of you are incredibly skilled
at working together with your teammates.
That day, a forceful draft snatched it away
I realized that you were the only ones I could count on
to fight without me there.
Unable to change, I have to leave it behind
Go beat your opponent without relying on my strength.
I'm confident you can do it.
Come, outrace your fear
The message ends there.
Damn.
Face the unfamiliar sky and day on your own two feet
For once, there wasn't a single "I just did" in there.
I can tell just how much he wanted to encourage us.
And greet the sunrise
Leave the planning to me.
Misfortune gave rise to happiness
I'm not going to let that woman get away.
You saw a guidepost at the end of despair
You got it.
And now, it's lit with a single flame
Lily and I'll go after Olivia.
If you need, Mr. Johnny can track her scent.
Shake off the entangled past
That's as much as I can really help right now.
And fight until you find a place your heart can soar
You've already done plenty.
If it weren't for your little ones,
we all woulda died back there.
Ah, surviving through each moment
Let's go prove ourselves, shall we?
We're plenty great on our own, even without Teach!
MISSION: Daughter Dearest IV
The moon that night was full,
just like it is tonight.
I was born in a small country to the east.
I spent my days as a prostitute
out in the backcountry,
and I always assumed that my life
would end there just like it began.
You're up.
My gun has a silencer, but even so,
it takes a bold spirit to sleep through
something like this.
Now, I'm going to need you to jump out that window.
You went mad, stole a gun that
one of your johns happened to have,
and went on a killing spree.
Then, you jumped to your death.
That's the plot of this little story.
This is what happens when a politician like him
chases after too many skirts.
But why kill all the others?
If a single politician died,
it would look like the work of an assassin spy.
If a bunch of unrelated people die, though,
they'll write it off as a regular old tragedy.
Now, hurry up and jump.
If you're lucky, you might even survive.
Those eyes of his were so different
than all the uninspired gazes I'd seen before.
It was like he was a prince from another dimension.
They took my frigid body
and gave it warmth once more.
Please, take me away from here.
You've got a knack for this.
Roland was a master assassin feared the world over,
and I became his apprentice.
I had days full of slaughter, jaw-dropping wages,
and sublime affection from the best assassin around.
I could never have gotten any of that out in the sticks!
There's a man you need to watch out for.
I told you that one of our spies took out Inferno, right?
Well, one of its members survived.
At the moment, that man is the most
dangerous individual in the Din Republic.
Bonfire, the Dust King, Ax, Lone, Practical, Crowbar...
He goes by many names,
but the most common one he uses is Klaus.
If you run into him, get in touch with me immediately.
That's a good idea.
No spy from a backwater nation like this
would stand a chance against you.
No, this man's skills are on par with mine.
He could well become my rival.
Your rival?
Even with how talented you are?
Be careful around him, my beloved.
Look at that, you survived.
Pretty sloppy of you not to confirm your kills.
Or what,
was there someone you were so scared of you wanted
to get away as fast as you possibly could?
There's no need for us to get the boss involved.
I'll take you on myself.
Looks like that explosion just now
messed your right arm up pretty bad!
Lotta confidence, comin' from someone
who was so scared of our boss she went running!
Only because Roland acknowledged
Bonfire's strength!
"Roland"?
The man you people were calling Corpse.
I never want to hear that ugly name
out of your mouth again.
Sorry, but if you're lookin' for the gun
you had strapped to your thigh,
I just nicked it.
But my surprise attack was perfect!
Constantly watching out for hostility
is a basic best practice.
Didn't Bonfire teach you that?
This is some impressive poison.
See, this is why I hate prodigies.
Wouldn't you agree, Teach?
You're wide open!
You fuckin' dumbass.
You can have this one back, too!
Why was it those two coming after me
instead of Bonfire?
Was Bonfire never here in the first place?
But then, that man I saw...
must have been the one member of
their team who wasn't there.
I'll put you out of your misery, you crazy bitch.
C'mon, Sybilla, up and at 'em.
I thought I was a goner there.
Take it easy.
That poison puts your body into a
state of suspended animation.
I'm fine 'cuz of my resistance, of course.
Did we manage to trick her?
Yup, everything went right according to plan.
Olivia headed back to the mansion.
Is Grete really gonna be all right?
Fighting ain't exactly her strong suit.
Oh, I don't think there's anything to worry about.
There you go, bein' happy-go-lucky again.
I mean, her resolve's on a whole different level.
So are her plans, her instructions, her leadership,
and the way she props up her heart.
If Olivia makes it back to the mansion,
I'll finish her off myself.
Now, it's her job to complete the mission.
She impersonated Teach himself and
took everything on her back.
There's no way someone with a heart
that strong would ever lose!
All we have to do now is believe in her,
in our strategist.
Go on and do great things, girl.
Win Teach's praise and his love.
MISSION: Daughter Dearest IV
It's okay.
Lily and Sybilla will be fine.
Everything so far is just as I expected.
But I feel like I'm going to be crushed
under the weight of my own fear.
Is this the responsibility the boss has to shoulder?
Would it be all right if I made one request?
Once I complete the mission,
would you hold me in your arms?
It doesn't have to mean anything.
I just want something to help me keep going.
Very well.
It's a promise.
When you come back alive,
I'll hug you as tightly as I can.
I won't run away.
I killed Sybilla and Lily.
If I kill you too, I'll be able to
go back to my job at the mansion.
What?
My job's to take information from Uwe
and pass it along to Roland.
I want to be useful to him.
Now, let's do this.
To the death!
Not good enough by half.
What has Bonfire even been teaching you?
I see no reason to answer that question.
Has he ever made love to you?
Roland's made love to me countless times.
He's showered me with affection,
taught me new skills,
and given me everything I ever wanted.
Oh, how unloved you are.
It's pathetic, really.
That was you in disguise, wasn't it?
That Bonfire I saw?
So, how are planning on using that
talent of yours to take me down?
Jump.
You want me to jump?
You're planning on making it look like I killed myself?
That will let me pin the blame
for Lily and Sybilla's deaths on you.
Now do it, or I shoot.
Lucky you!
Once you're dead, your teacher will finally love you.
Even my death wouldn't be enough for that.
The boss doesn't harbor
any special feelings towards me.
I've known that for a long time.
You really are pathetic, aren't you?
But he made me a promise.
I can't afford to die.
I have to survive if I want the boss
to hold me in his arms.
Well, bad news.
This is the end of the road for you.
Now, hurry up and-
But how?
I didn't sense any hostility.
If I did, I would have been able to dodge the bullet!
Of course you didn't feel any hostility.
That bullet was meant for me.
I know you're up there, killer scum!
Damn it, he escaped again!
It's dangerous out here!
You need to get inside!
Wait, who are you?
What a letdown.
Having the target jump to their death?
I can't believe you took Corpse's signature move
and used it verbatim.
I guess you can only mimic what you were taught.
I'm code name Daughter Dearest.
Now, let's fill this time with laughter and tears.
That birthmark...
The reason I let Uwe see me as the assassin twice
wasn't just to root you out.
It was so he would fire at this birthmarked face
without hesitation.
I'd already made sure that his marksmanship returned
as his night blindness abated.
I knew that his bullet, aimed at the assassin,
would come flying straight at me.
All I had to do was dodge,
and a bullet devoid of hostility
would strike you directly as you stood behind me.
That's impossible.
What part of it?
There's no way you could have
donned a disguise that quickly!
I never gave you a chance to put on a mask!
I didn't put on a disguise.
I did the exact opposite.
I took one off.
Taking off a mask is so easy,
you can do it in an instant.
This is my real face.
This is why nobody ever loved me.
I get it.
It all makes sense now.
So, that's why you're so needy.
No wonder you're so unloved!
See, the thing about women who are loved
is that we don't have to fight ourselves because
we have men who protect us.
A transmitter?!
The moment I saw Bonfire,
I called Roland in to save me.
That turned out to just be you in disguise,
but it all worked out for me in the end.
If you kill me, he'll go mad with rage
and go on a wild rampage.
Because he loves me!
This changes nothing.
It's just as I expected.
Everything is going how I expected.
This time, you're dead!
You can take that hideous, unloved face of yours
with you to the grave!
What a sorry woman you are.
I can't begin to comprehend it.
How can you see her face and not feel anything?
Bonfire!
Even now, I can clearly remember
the sight I saw that day.
The moment I saw her naked face,
I understood everything.
I could tell just how intently she'd built up
her techniques in order to obtain love.
I could tell how much she'd honed herself.
Her face spoke of a radiantly magnificent heart,
and I found myself enchanted by it.
That's why I couldn't help but say,
"How beautiful."
Where's Roland?
Right there in front of you.
Olivia?
But how?!
You said you were evenly matched with him!
Evenly matched?
That reminds me, I had a question.
As soon as I ran into him, he starting babbling
some nonsense about us being rivals.
Do you know what that was about?
What do you mean?
I mean, he was a pushover.
As the World's Strongest, he was no match for me.
He's lying, right?
This isn't really happening, right?
Please, Roland, say something!
Olivia...
Save me...
No, no! Why is this happening?!
Grete...
On it, I came prepared.
You two have taken too many lives.
Shadow war or not, your actions are unacceptable.
I hope you've made your peace.
My peace?
He never taught me about this.
I see.
Now I understand why you lost.
You people aren't qualified to be our enemies.
I've been watching the night as it pours on down
Even as it gets closer and closer
(Give it up, give it up)
If I quietly gave you my secret name
I could vanish into the dark to avoid being found
I've forgotten all about those secret tears I shed
Like my cells all got replaced
I'm a different person now
So let's frolic our way through these busy days
I kind of want to talk to you
But everyone is gone
That's not what it means
To make someone a promise
I've been watching the night as it pours on down
Even as it gets closer and closer
(Give it up, give it up)
If I quietly gave you my secret name
I could vanish into the dark to avoid being found
And when we're born again
Flying through a new night sky
We intersect again and again
Standing on level stars
And gazing straight into each other's eyes
I want to give it to you when we meet again
The mission's finally over,
so let's end it by going for a drive together.
I do believe it was Lily who made that suggestion.
It was.
That girl lies as easily as she breathes.
Thanks to my bold scheme,
Grete's probably sobbing with gratitude
right about now!
Do you think she's actually crying?
Hell if I know.
Still, she worked her ass off this time around.
I'd say she's earned this much.
Grete, I've done a lot of thinking over this past month.
I was trying to figure out what the best way for me
to respond to your love would be,
both as your boss, as the Greatest Spy
in the World, and as a man.
Were you able to reach a conclusion?
I was.
I decided to ignore all my ideals,
responsibilities, and pretenses
and tell you how I truly felt as a man.
Grete, I hold no romantic attraction towards you.
I can't return your feelings.
I see.
However, I don't want you to misunderstand me.
I've never felt romantic attraction towards anyone.
Romantic love isn't what I'm looking for.
What I want is familial love.
The kind of bonds that form over the course of both
harsh missions and peaceful downtimes.
That's why I can't return your romantic love.
I can't love you as a woman,
and if you end up developing feelings
for some other man,
then I'll have no right to get in your way.
But if you're willing to stay by my side,
then I would like very much to love you
as a member of my family.
I have a request.
Could you say something?
Please, tell me how you see me.
There's only one thing I possibly could say.
Grete, you're beautiful.